businessol.com 2018-09-10

# Privacy Policy | BusinessOnline

BusinessOnline respects and protects the privacy of its customers. Therefore, we would like to share with you the following practices that govern how we use, share and protect the information you provide to us through our Website.

### Personal Information

BusinessOnline collects personal information (such as names, telephone numbers and email addresses) only from visitors to our Website that fill out the BusinessOnline “Get a Quote” Registration form. If you fill out the Registration form, the personal information provided by you to BusinessOnline could be used by us to process your order, initiate contact with you regarding your request for a quote, deliver services, send you newsletters and updates and other information, update our records, communicate with you about our services and generally maintain your accounts with us.

### Security Measures

All Registration information provided by you is stored by BusinessOnline in a password protected database on a secure server. However, no Internet or e­mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e­mail sent to or from our site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e­mail. Although we take commercially reasonable measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet.

### Opt Out

BusinessOnline may also use your contact information to tell you about products or services that we think might interest you or to invite you to participate in a product or service-related survey. In all instances, you will have the option of opting out and/or unsubscribing from BusinessOnline’s e-mails. Because the nature of our business does not appeal to children under the age of 13, we do not knowingly acquire or receive any information from children.

### Sharing of Information

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may share your personal information with third parties to provide products, services and content you’ve requested, when we have your permission or under the following circumstances:

  * In the process of fulfilling your orders or your use of our services, BusinessOnline may by necessity provide some of your information to third parties.  We may occasionally employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf for business purposes.  Examples could include, without limitation, sending postal mail and email, providing services, gathering or analyzing data and providing marketing assistance.  These companies will have access to your personal information only to perform their functions and may not use it for any other purpose.
  * BusinessOnline might share your personal information with its third party partners who might initiate contact with you to deliver content and to provide updates and communications regarding their products and services.  You will have the right to opt-out of or unsubscribe to any such email contacts.
  * We may share your personal information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy.
  * In the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition or dissolution, personal information could be shared or become one of the transferred assets.  Any use of personal information by such third party transferee would then be in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy or the transferee’s privacy party.
  * BusinessOnline may disclose your personal information if we believe we are required to do so by law, court order, subpoena from a court with proper jurisdiction, regulation or other government authority or otherwise in cooperation with an ongoing investigation by a governmental authority or agency.

## Automated Information Collection

### Use of Technology Cookies

BusinessOnline may track visitor activity to our Website using IP addresses and set temporary cookies to track user sessions.  Cookies are small data files that write to your hard drive when you visit the site.  We use cookies to track user traffic patterns and hold certain registration information.  This data helps us keep track of the number of visitors to our Website and facilitates the dynamic nature of our site. We may link information we store in cookies to personal information you submit while on our site. Cookies also allow us to make your visit to our Website easier by recognizing you when you return and provide you with a more customized experience.  Cookies might, for example, collect your IP address, browsing behavior and referring URLs.

### Web Beacons

BusinessOnline also uses a “Web beacon” technology, which generates an anonymous notice when a visitor accesses a web page on our Website. Web beacons work in conjunction with cookies to let us know what portions of our Website are of interest to our visitors and to help us provide you with tailored information from our website.

### Web Analytics

In addition to BusinessOnline, our web analytics providers may collect and track information on our Website using the technologies described above. The privacy policies of these third party providers will govern their use and collection of this information.

### Do Not Track

If our Website receives a “do not track” request from your browser, BusinessOnline will not track your information.

### Third-Party Privacy Policies

Please be aware that other websites that can be accessed through our Website may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party websites linked to the BusinessOnline Website are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

### Correcting or Updating Personal Information

If you have any questions or concerns regarding BusinessOnline’s collection, use or disclosure of your personal information or if you wish to change or review your personal information, please contact BusinessOnline for assistance at:

BusinessOnline  
701 B Street, Suite 1000  
San Diego, CA 92101  
legal@BusinessoOL.com

We will generally respond to your request within 30 days.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

BusinessOnline may change this Privacy Policy by posting an updated or revised Privacy Policy on our Website 20 days before the change will go into effect.  Please check this Privacy Policy periodically so that you will remain up-to-date.

Last Updated:  January 7, 2014
